Mss.B.B28.w Mss.B.B28.w
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to John Bartram, May 10, 1766; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768; Fothergill, John, 1712-1780
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 4:20.
  - Letter to Peter Collinson, June, 1766; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 1:49. Darlington's Memorials 281.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Aug. 21, 1766; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 3:65. Darlington's Memorials 282.
  - Letter to Peter Collinson, Aug. 26, 1766; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 1:49. Darlington's Memorials 283.
  - Letter to Peter Collinson, Dec. 18, 1766; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 1:66.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Jan. 3, 1767; Gale, Benjamin, 1715-1790
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 4:13. Darlington's Memorials 443.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Feb. 10, 1767; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:66. Darlington's Memorials 286.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Feb. 17, 1767; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 3:79. Darlington's Memorials 298.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 31, 1767; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Mill Hill, Typed L. 4p. (see Wildman. Correspondence of Bartram: pp.673-676.) Refers to Franklin. Printed in part: Darlington, 291-293.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Sept. 19, 1767; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Mill Hill, Typed L. 2p. (see Wildman. Correspondence of Bartram: pp.677-678.) Refers to Franklin. Printed in part: Darlington, 293-294.
  - Letter to John Bartram, 1767?; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:80. Some observations and remarks on thy journal, a reply at leisure.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Dec. 25, 1767; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 3p. Bartram Papers 3:71. Darlington's Memorials 295.
  - Letter to Peter Collinson, Jan. 24, 1768; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 1:54.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Feb. 12, 1768; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 3:72
  - Letter to John Bartram, Feb. 29, 1768; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 3p. Bartram Papers 3:75.
  - Letter to John Bartram, May 17, 1768; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:76. Darlington's Memorials 298.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 6, 1768; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 3:77. Darlington's Memorials 300.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Jan., 1769?; Fothergill, John, 1712-1780
    Typed. 3p. Bartram Papers 4:19.
  - Letter to John Bartram, May 1, 1769; Fothergill, John, 1712-1780
    London, Typed L. 4p. (see Wildman. Correspondence of Bartram; pp.694-697.) Refers to Franklin. Printed: Darlington, 339-341.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 2, 1769; Wrangel, Charles Magnus
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 4:114. Darlington's Memorials 444.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 9, 1769; Franklin, Benjamin, 1706-1790
    Typed. 1p. Darlington's Memorials 403.
  - Letter to Charles Linnaeus, 1769; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Typed. 7p.
  - Letter to John Bartram, March 1, 1770; Collinson, Michael
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:81. Darlington's Memorials 446.
  - Letter to John Bartram, 1770; Fothergill, John, 1712-1780
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 4:18.
  - Letter to John Bartram, March 3, 1770; Fothergill, John, 1712-1780
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 4:22. Darlington's Memorials 343.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Jan. 9, 1771; Collinson, Michael
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:83. Darlington's Memorials 447.
  - Letter to John Bartram, March 23, 1771; Hope, John, 1725-1786
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 4:54. Darlington's Memorials 435.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Jan. 8, 1773; Collinson, Michael
    Typed. 2p. Bartram Papers 3:82. Darlington's Memorials 453.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Feb. 16, 1773; Freeman, James
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 4:5. Darlington's Memorials 461.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Aug. 31, 1773
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 4:112.
  - Letter to John Bartram, Dec. 20, 1773; Freeman, James
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 4:6. Darlington's Memorials 462.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 12, 1774; Chalmers, Lionel
    Typed. 1p. Bartram Papers 1:103, 104.
  - Letter to John Bartram, March 27, 1775; Bartram, William, 1739-1823
    Typed. 3p. Bartram Papers 1:78.
  - Letter to John Bartram, July 15, 1775; Freeman, James
    London, Typed L. 1p. (see Wildman. Correspondence of Bartram; p.725.) Refers to Franklin. Printed: Darlington, 463.
  - Letter to John Bartram, March 18, 1857, [1757]; Collinson, Peter, 1694-1768
    London, Typed L. 2p. Add: "To Ben'm Franklin Esq in Philadelphia." (see Wildman. Correspondence of Bartram; pp.443-444.) Printed: Darlington, 214.
  - The correspondence of John Bartram, 1954-1955; 11" x 8 1/2"; Bartram, John, 1699-1777
    Charter Member of the American Philosophical Society, ed. by Edward E. Wildman; T.D. 719 leaves, 35p. of photostats Done in part by F.D. West. Deposited by the editor, grantee, Jan.1956.